Biology Prep Room
Mr. Takahashi, um...
（町(まち)）
先生 あの…
先日は ありがとうございました
Thank you for your help the other day.
O-Oh, no problem.
（高橋(たかはし)）
あ… ああ　大丈夫だ
もう風邪はすっかりいいのか？
Is your cold better now?
Yes, thank you. I'm all better.
（町）
はい おかげさまで
もう すっかり
Oh, good.
（高橋）そうか
Mr. Takahashi?
（町）先生？
Er, sorry. I was just...
（高橋）ああ いや すまん
なんというか
不思議な光景だなと思って
Thinking about what an odd sight this is.
（町）ん？
♪〜
I want to talk...
About your Wonderful Original
Interviews with Monster Girls
The class is astir
I want to let myself go too,
But I end up putting on a fake smile.
Your eyes alone conveyed a competitive spirit
Biting at your lip forcefully.
You once said,
"I wouldn't want to worry what someone thinks
And end up hurting someone else in the process!"
When the chime rings out, as the rain lifts up,
We'll pass the boundaries of our school!
Jumping through the puddles, light will scatter about
Our smiles, and wishes will be so bright!
I want to talk...
About your Wonderful Original!
〜♪
Machi Kyouko.
（高橋）
町 京子(きょうこ)　彼女はデュラハンである
She's a dullahan,
an Irish demi, whose legend is rooted in fairies,
アイルランドに伝わる
妖精にルーツを持つ—
and whose head and body are separate.
頭と胴体が分離したデミだ
Dullahan Wants to Be Coddled
Is it safe to touch the flame
coming from your neck?
その頭の炎って
触って平気なのか？
（町）え？
Is it hot?
熱くないのか？
N-No... Would you like to touch it?
えっ ええ
触ってみますか？
うっ
You're right. It doesn't feel hot at all.
（高橋）確かに 全く熱くないな
It's more like grabbing air.
虚空をつかむような
この世のものではないような
Feels strange, like something out of this world.
不思議な感覚だ
うう〜
Wh-What's wrong?
（高橋）ど… どうした？
触られると
神経が圧迫される感じがして
Touching it puts pressure on my nerves.
It's very uncomfortable!
つらいんです
S-Sorry... If you just tell me, I'll understand.
（高橋）
す… すまん
口で言ってくれれば分かるから
Your body isn't a separate being, right?
体は別人じゃないんだよな？
No, it's just my body.
はい　私の体です
See? See? See?
ほら ほら ほ〜ら〜
Whoa, it is true!
（高橋）
うわっ ホントだ
うおお〜！
See?
What's the matter?
どうしたんですか？
いや　ああ…
そういや この間 倒れたとき
Nothing. Uh...
By the way, when you collapsed,
was it all right to carry your head and body separately?
頭と体 引き離しても
大丈夫だったのか？
Yes.
ええ　最長で 東京と岡山まで
離れたことがあるので
They've been as far apart
as Tokyo and Okayama.
Okayama?! That's really far!
岡山！　遠いな
一体 どうして？
What happened?
My grandparents live in Okayama, so I visit them every year.
（町）
母方の実家が岡山で
毎年 祖父母に会いに行くんですが
But saying goodbye on the train platform was so hard,
駅のホームで別れを惜しむあまり
my body took off without my head.
体だけ乗せた新幹線が
先に出てしまって
I see...
（高橋）
なるほど
う〜ん 常軌を逸するな
日常生活で困ることもあるだろう
This is pretty crazy.
I'm sure it must be troublesome in your daily life.
I work through those issues with my family, using trial and error.
そういったことは失敗しながら
家族と試行錯誤ですね
It's all about experience and ingenuity!
経験と創意工夫です
Ah...
（高橋）ほほう
For instance, when I eat,
例えば 食事のときは
こういうので固定しますし
I hold it in place, like this.
When I use the bath or toilet,
お風呂やトイレなんかは
これでぶら下がりますから
I hang it like this, so there's no problem.
問題ありません
This is very informative...
（高橋）勉強になるなあ
Thankfully, I'm able to handle most things on my own.
おかげさまで 大抵のことは
１人でこなせるようになりましたが
But, my biggest struggle, is interacting with others.
なかなか難しいのが
人づきあいですね
人づきあい？
Interacting?
Yes, when people see me for the first time, they're startled.
ええ やっぱり初めて見る人には
びっくりされるようで
So getting comfortable with one another takes time.
打ち解けるには時間がかかります
今の時期は特に
Especially at this time of year...
Right, since you just joined this school.
（高橋）入学したてだもんな
I got sick and missed the entrance ceremony.
なのに 風邪ひいて
入学式に出れなくて
Then I missed three days.
そのまま３日も休んじゃって
I forced myself to come to school,
無理して学校に来たんですけど
結局 倒れちゃったんです
but I ended up collapsing.
No wonder I hadn't seen you around.
どうりで俺が気付かなかったわけだ
Hikari is different,
ひかりちゃんは別ですが
but I feel like there's some distance between my classmates and me.
ほかのクラスメートとは
少し距離を感じます
It's not like we don't talk,
しゃべったりしない
わけでは ないんですが
but they seem to avoid anything related to dullahans.
デュラハンの体質の話は
避けられている感じで
I would feel better if I could joke with them
本当は 体質のことで
冗談が言い合えるくらいのほうが
about my dullahan aspects.
気が楽なんですが…
（高橋）そうか
I see...
Machi.
（高橋）町
（町）あっ はい
Y-Yes?
Do you ever make jokes like that yourself?
お前からは
冗談を言ったりするのか？
Huh? No, I don't.
（町）あっ いえ 私からは
You don't?
そうか
Then, maybe that's where you should start.
じゃあ まず そこから始めると
いいんじゃないか？
I should?
そこから？
そういう仲を望むなら
If that's the sort of friendship you want,
you should tell some jokes to set a tone,
これくらいの冗談なら
許容できますよと
so they'll know what kinds of jokes you can share with them.
お前のほうから冗談を言って
線引きしてやればいい
なるほど 冗談ですか
I see. Jokes, huh?
In short, it's all about who takes the first step.
（高橋）
つまるところ 最初の一歩を
どっちが踏み出すかという話だ
Thinking of it that way,
your classmates have the higher hurdle to clear.
そう考えると
クラスメート側のほうが
ハードルが高い
Right, since I'm a dullahan!
私 デュラハンですからね
ハハハッ
You're probably the first real, live dullahan they've seen...
本物のデュラハンを見るのは
まず初めてだろうからな
Aren't there only three in the whole world?
確か世界に３人しかいないんだろ？
Huh? Yes, that's right.
えっ？　ええ そうです
よくご存じですね
I'm surprised you know that.
Well, I've done my research.
まっ いろいろ調べたからな
大切な生徒のことだし
All for my precious students.
Mr. Takahashi, um...
（町）先生 あの…
（高橋）うん？
W-Well...
（町）
あっ い… いえ　嫌だったら
If you don't want to, feel free to decline, but...
遠慮なく断っていただいて
結構なのですが
ああ その…
Um...
んん〜！
W-Would you please hug me?!
だ… 抱き締めてもらっても
いいですか？
Was that a joke?
（高橋）冗談？
No... Only my head.
（町）ではなく 頭を
（高橋）頭を？
Your head?
こうか？
Like this?
Y-Yes! Exactly like that...
（町）
うわ〜っ そ… そうです
こ… こうされるのが好きで
I... I enjoy being held like this,
and my parents often used to do it.
いつもは
両親にしてもらってたんですが
But now that I'm in high school, they told me to get over it.
高校生になったんだから
我慢できるようになりなさいと
言われてしまって
But I just can't,
でも 我慢できなくて
ほかに頼れる人もいなくて
and there's no one else I can ask...
そうか
Okay.
Alone, a dullahan's head can't do anything.
（高橋）
デュラハンは
頭だけでは身動きひとつとれない
To get around,
移動するには 自身の体にしろ
人肌に触れる必要がある
it needs contact with others, even if that's its own body.
In other words, hating solitude is part of a dullahan's nature.
つまり孤独を嫌うこと自体が
デュラハンの性質であり
Biology Prep Room
Put another way, they get lonely easily.
言いかえれば さみしがりであり
This little dullahan still wants to be coddled.
デュラハンちゃんは
まだまだ甘えたいのだ
しかし あれだな
But you know,
一教師としては
ふさわしくない光景かもしれないな
considering that I'm a teacher,
this might look inappropriate.
そ… そうですか？
R-Really?
まっ 困った連中に
見つからなければ大丈夫だろう
Well, as long as no troublesome
pests see us, it should be fine.
Like stubborn higher-ups
頭の固いお偉方とか
or that chatty vampire...
あのおしゃべりな
バンパイア… とか
Or anyone... like that...
（２人）ああ…
（ひかり）クフ
Everyone!
みんな〜！　聞いて 聞いて〜！
Check this out!
Hey! Hey! This is big!
ねえねえ 事件だよ
I guess this means you're one of the dullahans now.
これで高橋先生も
デュラハンの仲間入りですかね？
Gather around, people!
Eh?
（高橋）え？
（町）首が飛ぶんじゃないですか？
Because your head's going to roll, right?
なんちゃって
That's a joke I can't laugh at!
（高橋）それは笑えない冗談だ〜！
Wait! Hikari!
待て ひかり〜！
Hey, listen! Mr. Takahashi was...
（ひかり）聞いて 高橋先生がね
（高橋）待て待て 待て待て！
Wait, wait, wait!
Thanks, Hikari.
（町）
ありがとうね ひかりちゃん
え？　なに 急に
For what?
I'm really glad I was able to talk to Mr. Takahashi.
高橋先生と話せて
私 ホントによかった
ウヒヒヒ いや〜
Oh, just seeing that panicked look on his face was enough for me!
先生のあの慌てた顔 見れただけで
わたしゃ 十分 十分
ウヒヒヒ あっ
Yukki!
ユッキー！
Takanashi...
（雪(ゆき)）小鳥遊(たかなし)さん
Ah, you're so cold! This feels great!
あ〜 冷た〜い 気持ちいい
Your home is this way, too?
ユッキーも
家(うち) こっちの方なの？
（雪）うん
（ひかり）じゃあ 一緒に帰ろうよ
Yeah.
Then, let's walk home together!
Oh, this is Macchi.
あっ この子はマッチーね
Macchi?
マッチーさん？
私 寄るとこあるから
I need to stop somewhere on the way.
Really? Can't be helped, I guess...
（ひかり）
そっか〜 じゃあ しかたないね
I'm really sorry. Bye.
ホントにごめんね　さよなら
バイバ〜イ
Bye-bye!
Isn't that Kusakabe, from class A?
（町）
Ａ組の日下部(くさかべ)さんだっけ？　雪女の
The snow woman?
Yep, that's Yukki.
（ひかり）うん ユッキー
She's a little shy, but she's nice.
ちょっと恥ずかしがり屋だけど
いい子だよ
Oh...
（町）へえ
And her body is so cold!
それに体が冷たくて
抱きつくと気持ちいいの
She feels so nice to hug!
Oh, so that's why you suddenly hugged her like that.
（町）だから 急に抱きついたんだ
（ひかりの笑い声）
My house is that way. Wanna stop by?
（ひかり）
私んち こっち　寄ってく？
Hmm... It's already pretty late.
（町）
う〜ん でも もう遅いから
Yeah, that's true.
（ひかり）
ああ 確かに
うちの人 心配するもんね
I bet your parents would worry.
Well, come over again when you have time to visit.
じゃあ また今度
ゆっくり遊びに来てよ
Sure.
（町）うん
Take care!
（ひかり）気をつけてね〜
（着信音）
ん？
Hi, Mom?
（町）
もしもし お母さん？
今 帰ってるところ
I'm on my way home now.
Sorry, I was talking to my teacher...
ごめん ちょっと先生と話してて
ううん そんなんじゃないから
No, it isn't anything like that.
Okay, I will. Bye.
うん 分かった　は〜い
（ひかり）う〜ん？
Right there. That should do it.
（町）うん こんな感じかな
フウ〜 高校になると
Now that I'm in high school,
it seems that both studying and
exercising will be a lot harder.
勉強も運動もレベル高そうだし
大変だな
My head... My head can't keep—
首が… 首が回らな… はっ！
My head can't keep up.
Use when I'm really busy
Mr. Takahashi was so nice.
高橋先生 いい人だったな
Interviews with Monster Girls
I hope I can talk to him again.
また話したいな
You want to go on a date with a guy?!
男の人とデートしたい？
いいじゃない！
That sounds great!
Let's do it, let's go! Let's attack right now!
やろうよ しようよ
今すぐアタック！
（町）
う… う〜ん
でも 向こうがどう思ってるか…
B-But I'm not sure how he feels...
It'll be fine! You're really pretty!
大丈夫だよ
マッチー 美人だもん
You have a nice figure, so just flash
your boobs, and he's yours.
スタイルもいいから
おっぱいチラリでイチコロよ
You think?
（町）そうなのかな？
煮えきらないなあ
何か後ろめたいことでもあるの？
You're so indecisive!
Something bothering you?
Well, I'm...
う〜 だって私…
デュラハンだし
a dullahan...
Why is being a dullahan a problem here?
なんでデュラハンだと
恋愛が不利になるの？
（町）はっ！
ねえねえ
Well?
Th-There are statistics to indicate such...
そ… そういう統計データが
ありまして
I heard there are only three dullahans in the world.
デュラハン
世界に３人しかいないって
聞いたけど
（町）う…
Didn't think that through, did you?
よく考えずに言ったでしょ？
Using made-up excuses to run away
makes you look pathetic!
でっち上げた言い訳で逃げるなんて
かっこ悪い
うう… 確かに
不利にはならないかもしれないけど
Well, maybe it wouldn't put me at a disadvantage,
but it isn't exactly an advantage—
別に 有利ってわけでも…
Sure, it is!
（ひかり）有利よ！
（町）え？
恋愛ピラミッドの
頂点に立っているといっても
It's no exaggeration to say you stand
atop the romantic pyramid.
過言ではない
Yes, for instance...
そう 例えば
エッチなことをするとき
When it comes to naughty things,
you're capable of some special techniques.
すごく特殊なプレイができる
（町）
うお〜！
すごいね ひかりちゃんは
You're amazing, Hikari!
Do you know a lot about that sort of thing?
そういうの
いろいろ知ってるんだね
ウフフ〜ン まあね
よく知らないで言ったけど
Yeah, well...
I don't actually know much.
Anyway, anyway...
そいでさ そいでさ
What kind of date do you have in mind?
マッチーは
どういうデートがしたいの？
Huh?
え？
You must have some kind of plan for your ideal date, right?
（ひかり）
デートのプランとか希望とか
あるでしょ？
W-Well, I guess...
え… えっと そうだな
私 デュラハンだから
Since I'm a dullahan,
こうやって頭を抱えられてるときが
I feel safer when my head is being held like this...
いちばん安心できるっていうか
好きなの
And I love it.
Uh-huh.
うん うん
So...
だから その…
It'd be nice to hang around with the one I like as he carries my head.
好きな人に抱えられて
ぶらぶらできたら いいなって
（ひかり）ぶらぶら
Hang around?
He can decide where we go.
（町）
その人の意思で行き先が決まって
見上げれば その人の顔があって
And when I look up, I can see his face.
The little movements could bring our faces closer together.
ふとしたときに顔が近づいたりして
（ひかり）
ふん ふん
Uh-huh.
I-It would be fun to do that.
（町）
そ… そういうのができたら
楽しいっていうか…
I guess that's about it.
そんな感じかな
フフフ〜ン 乙女やの〜
ほんで ほんで？
You're such a maiden...
And? And? Who is this prince who's captured your heart?
ウワサのマッチーのハートを
射止めたプリンスは誰？
え？　う〜ん あ… その…
Oh, uh...
Come on, 'fess up!
ほれほれ 言っちゃいな
言って楽になりな
It'll be a weight off your shoulders!
（町）た！
（ひかり）た〜？
Ta...
Ta?
Mr. Takahashi!
（町）高橋先生！
（町）え？
（ひかり）フン
え？　ちょっと ひかりちゃん？
誰に電話して…
Hey... Hikari?
Who are you calli—
ニヒッ
Wait! Why are you making that face?!
（町）
待って！　その顔は何？
ひかりちゃ〜ん！
Hikari!
Good! You're both here!
（ひかり）
うむ
ご両名 おそろいになられましたね
Takanashi
We're doing an experiment!
今日は実験です
You two will go shopping!
２人で買い物！
終わっても日が沈むまで帰宅禁止
And you can't return until sunset, even if you finish!
Got all that?!
よろしいですか？
Yes.
（２人）はい
Anyway, Macchi,
（ひかり）
それにしても マッチー
随分 気合い入れて来たね
you really went all-out, didn't you?
へ？
Huh?
う〜ん 普通すぎるかな
That looks too normal.
That's too childish.
これは子供っぽいし
That's a bit much...
気合い入れ過ぎ
う〜ん う〜ん… よし！
I got it!
Y-You think so?
そ… そうかな？
Your body will be staying here with me, though.
（ひかり）
でも 体は私と留守番だけどね
What?!
ああ〜！
マッチーの体は
私が責任を持って見ておきます
I'll take responsibility for keeping an eye on Macchi's body.
Off you go, then!
じゃあ いってらっしゃ〜い
そうだった ヘヘヘ…
I forgot about that...
Okay, you and I will go to the living room!
じゃあ 私たちは居間にゴー
って 体だけじゃ聞こえてないか
With just your body, I guess you can't hear me.
ハハハ アハッ アハハ
So what kind of experiment is this?
（高橋）
今日はこれ 何の実験なんだ？
Oh, um...
（町）
あ… あの…
す… 好きな人ができたら
I-If I ever find someone I like,
there might be chances for just my head to go out and do things.
いつか こうやって
頭だけで行動する機会が
増えるかなって
So I thought I should work out any problems in advance.
先に そのときの問題点を
洗っておこうと
Hmm, I get it. That's a great idea.
（高橋）
ほう なるほど
それは すばらしい
（ひかり）なんか そわそわしてる
She seems restless.
She's gesturing.
なんかジェスチャーしてる
私に見せられてもな
Showing me this won't do much good...
What are they talking about?
何 話してるんだろう？
Not long ago, the cherry trees here were in full bloom.
（高橋）
ここも ついこの間まで
桜が満開だったんだがな
It's all green now.
もうすっかり緑 一色だ
I wish I could've seen them blooming.
（町）咲いてるときに来たかったな
フフ
（ひかり）
ヒッヒッヒ
わりと うまくやってるみたい
Looks like it's going pretty well!
ん？　手帳？
A notebook?
You can write without seeing?
That takes skill.
器用だね　見えてないのに
あっ
"I'm having a great time. Thank you."
“すごく楽しいよ　ありがとう”
ウヒヒ
You're welcome!
どういたしまして
でも なんだか うまくいき過ぎて
But it might be going too well.
And that kinda ticks me off!
少し腹が立つ
コ〜ッ
くわ！　て〜い！
うわ〜！
Wh-What's wrong?
（高橋）ど… どうした？
えっ？　あっ いや ちょっと
思い出し笑いを
Oh... N-Nothing.
I just remembered something funny...
Something funny?
（高橋）思い出し笑い？
う〜！
（ひかりの騒ぎ声）
She's mad! She's mad!
怒ってる 怒ってる
アハハハ！
Well?
（高橋）で？
（町）は… はい
Y-Yes?
Have you found any problems yet?
（高橋）
何か見つかったか？　問題点
S-Sort of...
（町）す… 少しは
ん？　どうした？
顔色 悪いぞ
What's wrong?
You don't look so good.
Uh, no.
ええ はい
ちょっと酔いました ウプッ
It's just a bit of motion sickness...
ハア〜
You okay?
大丈夫か？
はい もう全然
Yes, I'm fine now.
Sorry about that. This is all new to me.
（高橋）
すまんな
こういう経験は初めてなもんでな
It's all right.
（町）
いいえ
あの 私も初めての経験ですし
Um, this is a first for me, too.
B-Being on a d-date with a guy, I mean...
こ… こんなふうに
男の人とデ… デートというか
一応
実験の成果はあったってことか
But that means the experiment did produce results, huh?
Y-Yes! The experiment!
はっ はい
実験！　実験です
やっぱり 実験してよかったです
This is an experiment!
I'm so glad I did this experiment!
ア… アハ アハハハ
Class A's Kusakabe?
（高橋）Ａ組の日下部？
（町）はい 雪女のデミで
Yes, she's a snow woman demi.
Of course I know her,
もちろん知ってるが
話したことはないな
but I haven't spoken to her.
What about her?
日下部がどうかしたか？
Wh-When Hikari and I were walking
home together, we bumped into her,
ひ… ひかりちゃんと帰る途中
たまたま会って
and Hikari suddenly hugged her.
ひかりちゃんが
日下部さんに抱きついたんです
Yeah, Hikari did say she clings to her a lot.
（高橋）
そういや あいつ
よく くっつくって言ってたな
And when she did, Kusakabe...
（町）そのときの日下部さんが…
Did something happen?
（高橋）何かあったのか？
嫌がってるというんじゃなくて
I don't think it was that she disliked it, but...
なんていうか…
怖がってるみたいな感じがして
She seemed almost scared.
Of Hikari?
（高橋）ひかりをか？
そういうんじゃないんです
No, not that.
I don't know how to put it.
うまく言えないんですけど
ちょっと気になって
But it just bothered me a little.
（高橋）
う〜ん 今度 話しかけてみるか
Should I try talking to her sometime?
うう… もう限界
I can't hold it any longer...
あっ
（トイレの流水音）
ああ！
（ひかり）あっ
Ow!
（町）痛っ！
（高橋）どうした？
What's wrong?
N-Nothing, really.
い… いえ 別に エヘヘヘッ
What's wrong, Macchi?
（ひかり）
どうしたの？　マッチー あっ
M-Macchi...
マ… マッチー！　あっ
Macchi, here. Write it down.
マッチー　ほら メモ メモ
“トイレ”
"Bathroom"...
なんだ トイレか
びっくりした
Oh! You just need to go to the bathroom?
You really spooked me!
（ドアが開く音）
（ひまり）ただいま
I'm home.
Sister, is someone visiti—
（ひまり）
お姉ちゃん　誰か来てるの？
There we go, there we go...
（ひかり）よ〜し よしよし よ〜し
（ひまり）
うわっ！　へ？　ええ！
なんかいる
Huh? Something's here!
There we go, there we go...
Take your time...
（ひかり）ごゆっくり〜
Whew, that was exhausting.
ハア〜　疲れた
Sister?
（ひまり）お姉ちゃん？
Oh, welcome back, Himari!
あっ おかえり ひまり
Who was that... person?
（ひまり）今の… 人は？
My friend Macchi. She's a dullahan.
友達のマッチー
デュラハンなの
Where'd you put her head?!
（ひまり）頭 どこやった！
ハア〜
見かけたときに
それとなく声をかけてみるか
Next time I see her, I'll just call out to her.
I shouldn't have had that juice.
ジュースなんか飲まなきゃよかった
Do you feel sick again?
また気持ち悪くなったのか？
Er, no, it isn't that.
あっ いえ 違います
な… 何でもないです
I-It's nothing...
エヘッ エヘヘヘヘ
How's this? Do you feel all right?
（高橋）
こんな感じでどうだ？
つらくないか？
Yes, this is much better than before.
はい　前より とてもいいです
先生 すごいですね
You're amazing, Mr. Takahashi.
I just remembered something I learned in school...
学生のときに学んだことを
思い出してたんだ
When people walk, their bodies move up and down.
人が歩くとき 体は上下するが
それを感じないのは
But they don't feel it because they
unconsciously move their necks
無意識のうちに
首や視線を動かすことで
and eyes to balance it out.
バランスをとっているから
なんだってさ
But for you, your arms function as your neck.
町にとっては腕が首なんだよな
I see... I'd never thought about that.
なるほど
考えたことなかったです
So you need to find a dynamic balance.
（高橋）
だから 力学的にバランスを…
ああ そうだな
Or, in simpler terms, be like one of those balancing toys.
簡単に言えば
やじろべえみたいにするんだ
Balancing toys?
やじろべえですか？
Yeah, like using this arm to correct camera blur...
（高橋）
ああ　この腕をな
カメラの手ブレ補正の…
Takanashi
Thanks for all your help today, Hikari.
（町）
今日はいろいろ ありがとね
ひかりちゃん
Yeah, I really freaked out that one time, though!
いや〜 あのときはホント焦ったよ
That one time?
（高橋）あのとき？
（町）わ〜！
Nothing! It's nothing!
何でもないです 何でもないです
Um, thank you for helping me with this, Mr. Takahashi!
あの 先生も おつきあいくださって
ありがとうございました
No, I should thank you.
いや 礼を言うのはこっちだ
勉強させてもらったよ
I learned a lot today.
Then the experiment was a success.
実験 成功ですね
Yep. A great success.
（高橋）ああ 大成功だ
Grmff sffsmfs!
（ひかり）大成功
Bye-bye!
バイバ〜イ　またね〜
See you later!
（ひかり）ねえ 先生
（高橋）何だ？
Hey, Mr. Takahashi.
What?
About Macchi...
マッチーのことなんだけど
ん？　町の？
What about her?
Principal, dullahans have carry their heads all the time.
（高橋）
校長 デュラハンは
常に頭を手で持ってますから
And carrying a regulation bag takes up one hand.
手提げかばんでの通学は
片手が塞がってしまうんです
It's inconvenient. Worse, it's dangerous.
不便ですし 何より危険です
For class 1-B's Machi Kyouko, couldn't you give permission
１Ｂの町 京子は
特例で 指定のかばんではなく
to use a backpack instead of the regulation bag?
リュックでの通学を
許可 願えませんでしょうか？
That's a good point. I didn't give that enough thought.
（校長）
ああ それは確かに
配慮が足りませんでしたな
Of course I'll grant permission.
もちろん許可しますよ
Thank you.
（高橋）
ありがとうございます
もう１つ お願いが
I have one other favor to ask.
What is it?
（校長）はい
We should also consider her
homeroom teacher's position.
担任の先生の立場もありますから
So could we just say this was your order?
これは
校長先生のご指示だってことに
（校長）
アハハッ なるほど 分かりました
I see. Very well.
Morning, Mr. Takahashi!
（ひかり）先生 おはよう
（町）おはようございます
Good morning.
Hey. Oh, a backpack?
（高橋）うっす　おっ リュックか
Yes. Yesterday, my homeroom teacher told me I could use this instead.
（町）はい　昨日 担任の先生に
リュックで通学してきていいって
言われて
You're looking good, Macchi!
（ひかり）
マッチー なかなか かっこいいよ
ねっ 先生
Right, Mr. Takahashi?
Yeah, it suits you.
（高橋）ああ 似合ってるぞ
（町）エヘヘ
♪〜
The events of a mysterious world,
Like the ones you hear of in fairy tales,
Are actually closer than you think
Just like the way you and I met!
When I stood up tall to gaze at
The familiar scenery outside my window,
Even days that felt like torture seemed precious somehow.
Stuck in my heart, I can't put them into words
How should I try to put these feelings into words?
Laughing over stupid things...
Getting mad over small details...
We'll keep carving these trivial moments into our hearts.
Sometimes I'm feeling sad...
But when I'm with you, I'm so happy!
We'll keep on building these irreplaceable moments,
And little by little, we'll come to understand one another.
〜♪
Next Time
Ms. Succubus is a Good Adult
Next time on Interviews with Monster Girls:
（ひまり）
次回「亜人ちゃんは
語りたい」
Succubus is a Good Adult.
「サキュバスさんは
いい大人」